Nguyen Thai Anh

Data Science - Al

HoChiMinh, Vietnam

INTRODUCTION

My name is Nguyen Thai Anh, I am currently graduated with a bachelor's degree in information technology with a very good degree. I am currently studying for a master's degree Data Science and AI at the Asian Institute of Technology. I have a passion for research and teaching in data science, machine learning, deep learning and can use English to communicate.

EDUCATION

Van Lang University August 2018 - July 2022

Major: Information Technology

---- GPA: 3.4/4

Asian Institute of Technology January 2022 - December 2023

Major: Master Data Science and Al

--- Studying

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant January 2021 - August 2022

4 Semesters

Subjects:

- Discrete Math
- Introduction to Big Data
- Introduction to Artificial Intelligence
- Probability Statistics
- Linear Algebra
- Machine Learning

School-level Scientific research

January 2021 - October 2021

2 Semesters

Topic: Build an integrated Plug-in in Moodle online learning software (E-Learning) to serve data analysis from log-files to support performance evaluation student learning outcomes.

Scientific research May 2021 - December 2021

2 Semesters

Paper name: Developing A Job Recommended System For Students In Information Technology Based On Learning Capability

Meeting The Needs Of Employers

Published in Fair

HONORS & AWARDS

Typical student	2020-2021
The valedictorian of the Faculty of Information Technology, second semester.	2019-2020
The valedictorian of the Faculty of Information Technology in the first semester	2021-2022

SKILLS

Language	English
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint

INTERESTS

I like music, machine learning, deep learning and natural language processing.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Programming Languages: Python Instruments: Piano, Guitar, Drums.